[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Tell me why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "No, I'm not angry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["General Douglas MacArthur", "Grant"], "PERSON": ["Patton", "Robert E. Lee"]}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "And indeed with the wider issue of America's place on the world stage and in the Middle East in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, first of all, you know, the old days, we had generals like Patton and Robert E. Lee and we had some great ones, General Douglas MacArthur, Grant.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Would you ever allow such a thing in your pageants Donald Trump?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, we allow them but we don't encourage it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What do you think of where we are with Syria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, I mean first of all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Military action?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I mean, I think that while we have peace process in place that may lead to the removal of chemical weapons, then I don't think we should strike.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "If it ends up with the chemical weapons being removed and being seemed to be removed from Assad but he stays in power, is that still a victory at any time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "CC", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "That would be a real win for international security if those chemical weapons were removed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Assad"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Are you a fan of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "You know, I'm not a fan of arbitrary rules that target certain classes of people, except criminals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Van Jones am I loosing the plot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Look on first blush it does sound totally preposterous and ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 237, "question": "I ask you both again, would you be happy for the veteran in the scenario that Van Jones just pictured for me to be a New York cab driver if they so wanted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "No I wouldn't but I'll tell you what Piers...", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Which one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "Watch tonight when Ricky Gervais enters my lair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "That's -- that's worrying isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "The chair in the lair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "What does it conjures up to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well it's scary because there is a man in a pink tie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "Did you ever think in your early chubby days, ever have that kind of headline in this six months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I could only hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "I like him, he's enjoying his food.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Would you see him as a figure of fun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yeah, no, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "Now how can you work out, given that I couldn't shake your right hand because of this terrible tendonitis you've got?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well I can run, I can run and it strapped up but I can't be wasting money so I ran, I still ran everyday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 309, "question": "You're in agony right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I'm on pain killers so...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "So, how many months have you have this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "A frozen shoulder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "What are the, you said the things you like, what are the things that really annoy you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Only two things really, really make my blood boil I suppose.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Gervais"], "LOCATION": ["Brighton"]}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 377, "question": "But how can you possibly review it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Yeah I had that ones in the tabloid, they were saying about Rick Gervais should be banned from television, his life I think disgust me, talks about just all of the holocaust right and it's then, my friends went to see him in Brighton, well no that's it...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Derek"]}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "But what was the purpose of this creation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well wanted Derek.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "You can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Subliminal twerking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Underneath I'm like a duck.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Well they're constitutional right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Would be damage if -- and they gave an example of, you know, if they were fully sighted and used the gun just because they lost their sight, why should they lives to constitutional right to continue having a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "So, the constitution covers everyone, does it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "Dallas"]}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "But tell me, you are not allowed to carry a gun?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "I would not be allowed to carry gun here in New York, but I could carry one in, you know, Dallas or I can carry one anywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Pick up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "That is the big one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "You've done it three times, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Three times, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "What is the -- what is the technique to handling that notoriously difficult crowd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "I think -- worry about the TV audience, do it for them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WDT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "The one that sprang to mind was the first Golden Globes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I don't know, 'cause I shouldn't have won it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130913pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN"], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What's the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "(inaudible)", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]